Beautiful America. Oh gosh, I'm sorry guys
Sorry hey, hey, who is that? Oh my god
Scared the hell out of me. Hey, how are you? I'm okay. How are you?
Are you streaming right now, what is happening?
What is it the new stream that you started? I don't know what's happening
This is weird. I can barely hear you too. I
Ended the other stream. Do you hear better now or is it yeah, I think what makes better a little better. Yeah, okay. Yeah
I started a new chat. Let me see. I started a new stream
I ended it and then I started a new one and then you appeared on the stage and I got
And there's Jamie's in the run. I think she found the new stream. See look I can show it on the stream next either
I can actually make us bigger. Hold on one second. Yeah, I can't see anything but us. Yeah, hold on like this
How about this? I can't see chat or anything. Am I supposed to?
Yeah, I think you can see I don't know if you can see it. Can you see it on your butt?
You can't see a backstage on yours. I can say chat. I see them back
This is people
People it says on the right says people maybe and then you can or it says chat on the right somewhere. I see it
Well, I see but it's just it seems to be just backstage
Yeah
Well, there's there's you there's to get to like your chat and then there's public chat and then there's probably the private chat
You know, so you can click on it. I don't know how to get the public anyways. Yeah
I'm okay. You guys
so you got the second stream going
yeah I said I said go live I started so it says I said I'm live is that there's
new there's people coming in the room I don't know was that was I just was I
just invisible because it said like something like oh well it says he ended
the stream but yeah yeah the display said live stream ended
But the stream was still live, and then you dropped the link to join, so I'm like, that's weird.
StreamYard, I'm always like just like leaving the studio and coming back in the studio, like it's always like, never like ends the show, and it didn't like say it ended it, it said, oh, go back into the show in progress, and then it looked like it was on like normal.
But it said it on the screen, that's the thing, that's why we're so confusing.
And not on my screen, so it's even more confusing, you know, it's like, it was, yeah.
Oh, yeah, it didn't for me, but um, yeah, I believe you a home is a chat saying what's
the same thing? Okay. Hey, so there's a studio chat and there's like the, um, the public chat.
I don't know if you can see that. Hey, Justin, how are you? Are you using Riverside?
You're the trash? Well, it's free for two months. It does like have some features.
It's like, it's not really trash. It's like
Well, the thing that is take just was I was in the studio when I came on like I gave the link and he's like
I didn't approve or anything. He's like, yeah, that's weird. I know we just have to be careful of a poor bum
Are gonna just come up in any second like I like him like, you know
But can't you just use the free stream labs? Why do you have to use the paid?
We should have this is like 20 hours and then you can continually make new accounts
But then I like I like to read I have like the referrals like on my own. I see okay
And I remember 20 hours no one's ever yeah, I think it's only 20 or 30 hours, but you can't even do multiple accounts or whatever
but I
Don't know. I don't need to like cheat the system like that. I mean, it's like I just like this is for free
It's like they I was I canceled it and they're like, oh how about two two free additional months? I was like, okay. Well
So then I that's just free to that's all it is three months. It's like it's like no matter if I wonder it's like it's just free so
Okay, and how much is it I think it's like 30 or 35 bucks otherwise like
And what's stream left or stream yard 45 dollars
Yeah, I don't know stream yard seems to be working better
You know, but I was paying $25 for stream yard for like six months and I got used to like doing that and then it's like then
I don't know. I just like to try and try new things. And this is like, I don't know, just stream yard is like a million dollar company. Hey, Jamie. So Jamie's Cowboys here just now. It's okay. It's like, I like the camera and like some of the stuff that does is fine.
You mark the clip easier. You mark, like put it like your like little, if you need to mark clips and whatever, you can put like a little note up like really easy, you know, and you do it so hard to do to tag.
the
but then the browser said to uh i had to install the app
okay well it's not like i promise it's not like something to like steal your identity or anything
yeah okay if i start getting uh strange letters from china and stuff i know where to go
well oh that was a good on mcdonald's copy yeah well i've been doing business with china
no i haven't that's why if i do start getting stuff from china
I'll know it's it's because of your uh your damn uh stream. Yeah
Blame psyche, right? Yeah, look at riverside FM. Look
What I don't see anything I just see me and you are you showing stuff on the screen? Yeah, I'm putting up banners and stuff
I don't see it at all. I can go like this. I can actually go like live with thing that is
That's what I'm going to put it in a home
live with
Thing
That is
Oh
Perfect, okay, and then I can save it and show it and I'll show it for like you can time put a timer on it
I'll show it for like how long I'll show it for like
I'm doing it for 10 seconds. Okay. Well, I'll show it again. Oh, I don't see longer
You know for 20 seconds, you don't see it. There is no I just see me and you that's it
Do you guys see it and you guys see it in the chat?
Does it say, hey Justin, does it say live with thing that is?
It's a very special guest.
You know what I don't like though? It's like, I want to share a presentation. It says presentation and it says like
there's like a little like thunderbolt nest to it.
I think it's like a premium, like an additional premium feature because it's not letting me click on it at all.
Oh, yeah.
presentation because I like to present like the videos I have and stuff but it's like
it's not not doing anything and if I go to media I have so I have some clips like these these clips
like listen to this
powered by riverside
And then we have this.
I want to get even crazier.
That's when you should have played when it came on instead of screaming.
I
Never used like the stuff they gave me for free. I mean I'd use my own stuff. Yeah, it was a little building with this
When he saw it look he's you can't see I can show the I can show the comments in the stream
No, I can't see you at no chat. You can see that. Oh, that sucks. Yeah, I'm on the screen either
No, nothing. So I'm wondering if it's just the app
Hey mermaid head Justin. Hey everybody like what are you guys doing? I'm sorry
Yeah, so thing that is is a good guess, but look I can go like this
Can you raise your hand like that see if I go like this? I want to talk. Let me talk
I can put my hand up like that. No, I don't know where I don't see it
You can't see it when I get a little hand on my on my thing
Nope. No, how about when I go like
Huh, like I cried you see that you see the no, man. I don't see anything. I see no graphics or anything just me and you that's all
Just me and you
Have you ever had a gay experience? No, would you like to have one? Nope with me? No
Yes, oh
My gosh, the screen just flashed. I think that's a sign
Your screen is I was
I was looking at the other stuff. I was looking at the browser to see if there was something
You just flashed me
So happy new year anyways, how are things and a few days to was it my birthday? Yeah in two days
Are you gonna jump out of a cake for me?
But I doubt it you doubt it. Yeah, what if I pay you for thousand dollars? No
You wouldn't do it for a thousand dollars
Not jump like it would have it
I mean just like we'll be in pastry to this thing where she got in the bikini and she sat on a cake like someone paid like
100 bucks and she like bought a $50 cake or whatever. She's like fell on it
Yeah, you know
Guys are weird we'll pay for like some weird shit much for you to be in a speedo and sit on a cake
Oh, I would get you don't have that much man. I don't are you sure? No
Yeah, pretty sure I've given what if a million dollars it's a thing about don't take more than that
a million dollars to be a speedo
a million dollars okay maybe maybe a million maybe it's like you know it's like you know
I'd have to think about it for a while I can't say for sure a million dollars I mean it's like
yeah I have to think about it it's not one of those things where I'm just gonna go okay
Yeah, you'd have pussy, you'd be so happy, it's not as much as in Canada.
No, you would be so happy, you would be so happy.
For what?
If you had money?
Oh, I thought you meant to see me jump out of a cake.
Oh yeah, well that too.
I mean, but I just want to know what design speedo are you thinking?
Well, if Canadian flag obviously like the Canadian flag, okay, and I can wear the American flag
We can have like our countries can duel
Shared border, right? This will be the best birthday ever
Share more than the border will share tongues will share spit. Oh boy now. We're getting too far
Why do you look so so like you look different though? Like I don't know
Like man more masculine or something
I'm on my phone. First of all, I'm I'm out of town. So my surroundings are different
No, no, my father passed away at a magical convention. Are you you're like, no, no
My dad my dad passed away today. Oh my god
It's not as bad as as you think like it's better
For him cuz he was in bad shape. I'm sorry. Oh my god
And yeah, I can't sleep I can't sleep I
Haven't been able to sleep for like the last couple days
I'm sorry, I mean, that's it's not that bad honestly, honestly, it's not that bad for that bad
It's like the first day, but it's like is you I wouldn't have jumped up. No, but it was we
We shut off the machine like he wasn't there. He he he had already
He had already
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. No such you like you're more upset about it than I am
He had already passed when like a few days ago when when he had his a
Whatever I think he had a heart attack jokes and stuff and like and like then and then it's oh, yeah my oh my god
That's like the worst
I actually feel a lot of relief after, you know.
Well, sometimes it's like that, but you know.
He also, he just found out that he had prostate cancer,
aggressively, an aggressive prostate cancer,
so he would have had to go through that stuff too, so.
How old was he?
80 86. Okay. That's how that's all my father was. Yeah. Yeah. Um, so that's pretty old. I mean, that's like, that's a good life. Um, yeah, because of, you know, because my father with your prostate cancer when he was in his 60s, I think, and he but he was able to like just get taking care of real quick.
And he lived another 20 very healthy years. Most of the most of the time until the very end. And yeah, I'm sorry, like Alex McQueen is saying he's sorry.
Thanks, I can't see Chad. I don't know what everyone's saying. Thanks. Oh, yeah, I'm sorry. I don't even know who's here
Yeah, it says Alexander McQueen money for 20. Jamie's Cowboys is here and mermaid is here
I don't know if everyone's still here, but yeah, you know the last few days I
Last few days. I wasn't feeling too good. I wasn't socializing and just kind of kept to myself, but today
I it's a sense of relief even with my sister we were talking and we both feel it
Well, I mean if it's like, you know, especially if they're suffering involved and stuff like that
That's the kind of like right when my father was like they just put in a bed and stuff like that
Yeah, there's a link hold on
I mean when you're just in the bed and you couldn't like get up and move and it's like you just knew you so miserable and he was just like
uh he he he wanted to go everyone was like putting medicine in his mouth and you know no one knew what
anything was but we're just trying to keep him alive for as long as we could but he would he
wanted to go and it's like and then he went pretty quickly like it because he was just like you
couldn't do it. Thing is my dad wasn't even he wasn't even conscious he had uh he had his heart
attack a few nights ago uh just just to add to the story he went out bashing he was uh drinking
retirement place I heard and he had a heart attack and he actually he died
right there like his heart actually stopped he was revived but he never
regained consciousness and then the MRI showed he had no brain brain activity
so he was already gone
Okay. Well, I mean, it's like, you know, you can come to, I mean, it's better if some people can come to terms with it. It's like, you know, it's, it's like, it's healthy. It's part of life, you know, is death and, you know, depending on like, we were belief of the afterlife or any of that, like, you know, you have a nihilistic view of the world or it's like, it's all meaningless and it's all just coincidence and random, or it's like, there's some kind of like, you know, order to the order to the universe and like, there's something more to it than just, I don't know.
You don't know that. Well, that's like what are you? I don't know. I don't I don't believe that there's some kind of a
I don't know how to explain it some kind of consciousness that that that's directing things or whatever you dream, right?
You have your dream. Yeah. Yeah, so it's some kind of a consciousness when you're unconscious
Well, it's still it's still my brain though
Sure, but it's like, well, our thoughts stored in the brain, they've looked at how it would
be impossible for all your thoughts to be actually stored in the brain, memory has to
be stored.
You said this the other day, and I say, well, no, it is very possible because that's what
happens.
But the brain is like this three pounds of like goop.
It's like, all our memories are lifetimes.
I don't know billions trillions. I don't know of cells of neurons and synapses and all that stuff
And you're saying you're very just a very scientific like we just evolved from monkeys and stuff
Well or apes or chimpanzees or whatever, right? And then it's like and we're like just another animal, right?
That's how it seems
It's like I can't say for sure. That's how it seems. That's what the evidence to me
So it says but I don't know for sure
in animals
Do the things that humans can do?
No, not to the same extent. No, we're definitely more advanced. Yeah
Yeah, well, they're very special. I mean animals have the special abilities, but it's like, you know, they do
Yeah, they do but our our brain power
Just makes us excel like we don't have to have the brute strength we our brains
You know
I can't hear you man, what sorry how much of our brains do you think we use like all of it you think we use all of it or
Small percentage of it like we have no we use all of it
Yeah, yeah, that old thing that you hear that, you know, we only use 10% of our brains, whatever. I mean, that's, that's nonsense. We use all of it is like, do we use like, do we use all of the United States or do we as a most of it mostly empty?
Well, okay, if you want to make the argument that a lot of the brain is just as empty.
I mean, like storage that hasn't, that hasn't been filled. I mean, okay, I'll, I'll accept that memories are stored in the brand personally. I'll accept that analogy, but
It's free. It's free for a couple of months and then let me just you can tell it's free
No one's been donating or anything. How am I supposed to pay for like all this?
The show is so expensive. I mean, it's like it's like way more expensive than I've ever made from it
But still I love it. You know, it's like yeah, and then my apps are all disaster
I mean, it's like it's so complicated
Like the but I do something called vibe coding and vibe coding is really cool and it's like really but it's like the coding is like
not always good. And there's different variations of quality of it. And it's like,
do you remember what I told you a little while ago that you do still have to know the coding to
know if it's if it's actually doing what you want? Well, yeah, but it's like, yeah.
That the vibe coding is can be complicated. It can be like more you can you know some code
It's still it's you learn some along the way
First like how to talk to it. It's like it's like I mean you can do vibe coding
It's like pure vibe coding and like do very well, but if you bet it's like
For the more like long-term like things you're gonna want to have like this like sturdy coding and stuff
but
Because but but actually I've been able to make some great things on it
But then I have like very fanciful like desires of like
Something as big as the media and then it's like it's very complicated to do and I'm deploying stuff. Hey, Amanda
No, you're not gonna do it Alex. Yeah, I mean it's like what what do you mean by vibe coding?
You mean to give it like it it takes it from start to end, right?
My coding is coding with AI, where you tell it what you want.
Okay. If it's just coding with AI, then sure, I vibe code all the time too,
but I only do little parts, like little things, right?
I don't tell it to build the whole app.
Yeah, exactly. It's just like people can use AI.
in a big variation of ways and they can use it a variation like the AI can have like a lot of
say in it it can have a very little of a say it can have like you know but it is like I think more
powerful when it's just like well well balanced between the AI and the human because I think they
work well together like it's like the AI can bring ideas into fruition it's like I'm able to animate
things now I would never be able to animate before I mean it's like not even not really animation
Images and things like that, but just like there's just being able to have the some kind of like intelligence that knows
Understands human beings on the level the coding models are just getting so much better and they're coming so much quicker
Yeah, it's good. It's getting better and better. I mean, I already see like it's just getting better and better already
I mean grok. I think grok just released 4.2, right today or yesterday
And apparently that's that's the the best coding AI right now
Yeah, so it just keeps getting better. So eventually it's going to get to the point where you don't have to know the coding at all
You just tell it what you want. Yeah, and it'll do it in front of them
Trading on all this is like a money for 20 just came up
Hey money. Oh hey money. What up thing? What up site? Hey, this is terrible
Hey money, how are you like well today? I'm ghost was in your chat and he was like I know when you were playing that stuff
It's like I know it's just like you know, it's I'm kind of funny in those clips
Whatever, I don't mind those clips and then goes
Yeah, I know money even said that that oh man, it's like you didn't get mad at me. I'm cool with
I played the video after the end of this but psychism
I'm trying to be funny, I'm trying to be funny in those clips, I'm like, you know, I was like,
yeah, they are funny. They're funny. It's, even if I'm not trying to be funny, it's like,
I'm like, I like to be funny, you know, it's like, as long as people are laughing, you know,
you should be able to laugh, laugh at yourself for those because they're not, they're not humiliating,
they're not like shameful or anything like that, you know,
But then Sweet Pea was like, oh, we made peace after Christmas.
And then she came to this chat, and I made a little video for her.
She asked me to and stuff like that.
She said, can you make me a song?
I made her a little video.
It was cute.
And then she was in the chat one night.
And I was like, OK.
I was like, you know, and I was like, it's what I said to me one night.
I was like, oh, so I said, I'm fine with Sweet Pea.
I think we're cool now.
And then Sweet Pea was like, oh, we're not cool.
We have a lot of all this, and I was like, whoa.
And it seemed like it was just like the bygones be bygones,
but it's like, no, it's like, I can never,
and then it's like, but Bita and I have to,
hey, what's up, Mason, how are you?
Bita and I have talks, and actually Bita and I,
I've gotten along a lot of the time we talked,
and that was really nice, because.
That was good.
You and Bita was on my panel.
Yeah.
That's the way it is.
We were like, first we were just like, you know,
in the same room, and then it's like, you know,
I went on her show a few times,
and she was like gracious, and.
Was that that's been in the last couple days, I guess that you're wrong with okay days ago. Yeah, I went to Alexandra's
I think I'm blocked on all my accounts on her chat now and oh, no
Yeah, I wanted to say happy birthday and stuff because it's weird the same birthday, but oh, yeah
Yeah, but she's not interested in talking. I'm like she said I was like toxic or
She said as long as I'm associated with miss
Public video. Oh, don't don't yeah, don't say it. I know you yeah, but that's what she said is I'm associated with her
I can't talk to her so whatever but
I don't know like that with a bunch of people like I love a bunch of people like like this guy
I'm grim reaper network who's always this nice British gentleman always on my show like I never had a problem with him
I was in a chat. He's like, oh, I don't like you anymore
You're bad and I don't like tarot cards. Well, there's no proof they were real
I said, what's wrong? I didn't know anyway. We were fine
Then he just turned on me like like just hates me and it's like what did I do to some of these people like where they're like
And people misunderstand me, they just question my intentions.
They think there's all these things said about me.
None of them are true.
It's all like exaggeration.
I mean, I have noticed people that are in your chat
and go on your panels and that are nice to you and all that stuff.
And I see them somewhere else.
And they're saying some iffy things about you.
I'm like, I thought you were.
cool with cycling
I catch people doing that all the time and some of them are my mods
That's why I had to unmod like a ton of people because it's like I just sit and see people in chat
I have to
Know you that
Yeah, I took years of well that one night
I thought you were like teasing me because I was like
I just saw that you're holding up your phone and like showing showing me like with my glasses like crooked
But then I was like I saw that it was in the context. It was supposed to be like funny
And then here it is that I was you weren't like
I'm just fine stupid things funny. I'm high
Aren't you money? I want to be funny funny one
No idea why I was like, you know, he flipped on me like for no reason like I really like I
Just was like, I don't know what like what it is. Like I don't I don't know if it's like
Isn't that weird that people will just like turn on you and stuff, you know, no, yeah, I don't know what's going on
I remember that stuff with the with sweepy
And, yeah, I was a little...
Just watched the show, I know,
but she just doesn't comment in the chat.
And then, like, there's other people
that just don't comment in the chat.
But it's like, I wish they would.
Like, I mean, I was...
All the of them, like, you know,
I'll verbally spar with people.
And I'm not mad at people.
It's like, I'm just, like...
tired of being, like, turned on.
I like explanation.
Like, Alexandra, she was, like, so cold,
where it's like, she's like,
I'm never gonna talk to you again.
And then it's like, that was it.
It was, like...
Well, how about like, can we get over it like the next day, maybe like, we know it was just like, it was just like, no time, it was just like, it's over, and then it's like, if I ever show up, it's like, oh no, you're bad, like, and I think she was saying, I'm like, evil, or something, it's about money.
Fund a little bit, I've seen that bitch, that bitch was crazy.
Yes, man, she is. I've been telling you that for a while, like.
We're born the same day.
And so we both have those unusual interests, and her interests are a little bit unusual,
minor unusual, right? What is it, the fifth? Fifth or?
The seventh. Seventh. Okay, I don't even know what day today is.
The fifth. Today's the fifth? Holy crap.
Yeah. I'm going to look at the date on my phone. You're having me confused.
Yeah, so today, today's the fifth. My birthday is going to be on this Wednesday.
or something like that, I think.
Or yeah, so it's Monday, so it'll be on Wednesday.
I don't know, I missed all Christmas and all everything.
I don't know, I hope for you all to have a nice...
I shouldn't be back home by Wednesday,
so if you are streaming, I'll probably drop by.
I believe someone foretold that, but I'm asking that because he asked me the last time I was on panel, let's see, what's going on.
You wear boxer briefs, I think that is, or Tidy Y's?
Boxer briefs.
You wear boxer briefs, okay.
I wore straight boxers for a little while, but...
Do you ever go naked?
What like in pants, you know, just any they go to bed sleep naked or going to go in the hot tub. Wow
What do I mean if I don't like to go in the hot tub naked? I don't these days because you know, like I mean I get people
I'm not living alone. I've got my uncle
There and he has a nurse that that comes by I don't want to be sleeping naked and
Yeah, you know, so no I I did it
when you know when I was living alone
What about you money you sleep naked you sleep naked early. What do you do naked money for 21?
Take a shower take a shower
Shower stream we should do a shower stream. I did that I got this I got in the shower on my speedo and I
That was on July 4th last year. It was a happy 4th of July.
Yep. Guys, do you remember that? That was great.
I think that is. Do you remember my speedo?
I remember your speedo. I don't remember 4th of July though.
You know.
Specifically, not specifically, no.
I just remember cursing you and the person who bought them for you.
I made a video and I woke up early in the morning and I clicked on it.
And I said, oh my God.
that's not the way I thought my day.
Jamie bought them, so that's who we have to blame for this.
Jamie. Easy, easy.
Easy, okay, okay, sorry.
Well, easy's in trouble now because he threatened Christine or something like that.
Apparently, yeah, that's what's happening.
Apparently, there's something else going on with...
Between beta and summer and shit. I don't know like I said, I missed the last few days
No, but
But I saw I watched a little bit of summer stream where she was
Talking about it. It's like holy shit. She's she seems really mad. So yeah, I mean, I'm gonna go
Yeah, we're always like friends then she comes back over she's like, hey, what's up? Let's just like we're fine
Yeah, yeah, I know she's like that. Yeah, but then I'm sure her her and beta will work it out, too
I just I don't know exactly has something to do with Christine and easy that that's what I'm getting
Um, let's see. Oh, Christina. Yeah, I understand it, but I'm not going to give in to it. Yeah. I don't take sides. I don't really care. I just like, uh, but I will cover stuff. But whatever they've been talking about today is like somebody got doxxed and like, uh, I don't know, it's just like, there's names I knew from the people, but it was just not too interesting for me.
Like, you know, it's like, let me see who like pebs and stuff like that. Oh
Who was talking about you Samans?
We had my pebs like like and the doxing somebody or something. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, I saw I saw Samans later stream tonight
Yeah, yeah, there's something going on about giving an address for somebody. Yeah
Yeah, that's as well bad. We're gonna stop with that shit
Yeah, I mean it's like and just like and also like you know just in general I think like you know
We should not like you be like wish like you know threatening anybody's life
And I know yeah, that's and I mean it's like no matter what our feelings are or whatever
It's like we can always like we should be able to be civil and like at least have each other's back in this
Stream reverse or whatever this
Ideally sure but that's just not how we are
like humans people
Well, that's the thing.
People have the ability to change and do better for the better
and to want to do better and stuff like that.
So I have faith in the human race or whatever.
So you're a little bit.
Faith to do what?
Faith to improve, eventually, and to have love win over hate
and have, like, you know.
Create a beautiful world again. I think but if we survive long enough. What if the what if they hate it gets to be so much?
It's a leather lesson. I think but I think then it's like reincarnation right to deal with it again
I think that we learn, you know, I think that it's like a yeah, you know constant pride
I've like I've like vowed to stay in like
The earthly existence until everybody else gets out. I'm like one of the I'll be one of the last people to like be out of here
You you vowed to you have control over that
We had in like Buddhism they believe it's called a boot of Bodhisattva bow and like yes, you just feel pledged
That's what you just make this pledge to be here for humanity and it's a great human chat with my mom up here
What's that? I know that that's what I said. I can't read chat man. I don't know what I don't know who's here
Or I see it. I see right here. You don't see it. No, I don't I
Don't know maybe did you have to install an app money here?
You thought at this actually email me. What the fuck you got right up, right?
Yeah, I did that
Yeah, I don't think nobody's gonna come on the show with this once they see
What the fuck?
Especially after the use of stream y'all if I just have my effort on the show. I'm doing good
But everybody stream yard back, you know guys if you can help me out with the donation or buy a reading or like just support me in some way
Like because it's like it is kind of like getting really expensive and I really want to do the show
But I'm just gonna be by focusing on like, huh? Yeah, are you gonna do some?
Alternating between stream yard and this or you're just gonna stick with this
Well, I mean, I'm just trying this one one more night. I'll do I have some free hours on stream yard
I'm just kind of mad at them right now
because it's like we keep like raising a price.
You got to keep doing your show, man.
You should be monetized.
You can get super chats.
I know YouTube don't pay, it's just people that pay.
I know that people in the people.
Super chats, they pay the streamer every month.
Standard or something.
Hold on, so I can pause up a little bit, yeah?
I mean, it's like, but now it's like,
maybe it'll get better, right?
I don't know.
But hopefully, if I play a show like,
If you got some hopefully you guys like some of these things I'm putting out and we'll like the 64 divine arts series
I'm gonna do and I'll do like one a day. I'll be really consistent bringing a lot. I got every 2800 subscribers
I got about 100 subscribers. That's really really cool, you know, and so
You know, I think I'm like bringing new people in I mean people and but I had like
5,000 over 5,000 likes on tick-tock in like 45 minutes
And then I was like how many likes do I have now like 10 likes or maybe most you know right now in the chat
I mean, it's like so crazy how it's like. Yeah, they're different
Tick-tock and youtuber totally different. Yeah, it's different, but it's still it's like it's like it's a crazy
difference, right
I didn't take yours, Amanda. I didn't take your wrench. Can I mod you from here? No, I can't I didn't
Wasn't personal don't take a person. I mean, I'll be over mod you
But I'm really like I need a mods that are like watching out for me because it's like not like it's just like a trophy or like a
Hold on. It's not just like
I think it's I need I need like the only thing I could do moderated for people that you actually drop a link or somebody
I could click a channel and copy a link. It's about it. I
Don't bring people for words. I don't block you know that
As all I do is drop links if I'm around
Okay, man, there you go
Okay, well
Nobody's gonna get me in my feelings. I'm not gonna hide nobody no time enough. I don't do that
Okay, let me see who else mermi. It's just in the helm. Okay. Thank you everybody
You know if you guys if you want to be considered for a mod you can let me know
But it's like I really need people like to have my back because I've seen mods talking bad about me in other chats and stuff
And I just like couldn't take it anymore. Like I was like I just need like people like entrusted mods and stuff, right?
That too much to ask I don't think so my frozen hold on. Oh, there I am I see
What type of bizarro shit is this? Hey, Goddy. Yeah, we're in we're doing we're doing we're doing um, what's it called?
Riverside we're doing Riverside assuming
Goddard, you let me go back to see me. Oh, this is kind of trash
Kind of yes
Powered by Riverside
The line of criminals
Well, so it's like the thing that is is like the Riddler money for 20 is like that, you know
There's the I don't see on a mask and I'm like joke something. It's like like church get on here. I can change the format here
It looks completely different on one phone and I'm watching another phone
You're watching the actual stream right money on the other phone
Yeah, I just I wanted to see if it rotates the entire thing, but it doesn't
Yeah, I can't turn my camera around. I've tried that already
Well, I'm sorry. I mean, it's like yeah. Oh, look at this. We there we go. How about that?
Nothing's changed here in the app nothing changes. It's just just the three of us. That's all
Yeah, I got two big screens. I'm a little corner a little screen in the bottom right. Yeah
Well, I'm gonna tell you I'm pretty sure nobody else is gonna come come up on this once they see they got a download of that
You know I have a great app. It's a wonderful app
It's not a great album. It sucks.
So we used to space on my phone.
They're perfect. Oh, why is it moving around?
I can't read chat.
I can't have YouTube open at the same time as this, right?
At least not on the phone.
I feel like when I used to do panels before I had my computer,
I'd need one phone to be on the panel and another phone to read the chat.
What is this?
Yeah, this is great. Well, you know, I started to stream when I was on my cell phone and I mean I streamed on my st- for myself
Yeah, crazy for like months
till I got a new computer with like a ghost on me computer like a few months ago and so
but
Yeah, I
was just on my phone for like months. I can't believe it. It's like kind of crazy
But I did it, you know
Well, here we are now now. We're on Riverside or whatever it's called everything
He's moving around like I guess it's what whoever's talking goes
The family nothing moving
The viewers see a movie
Is everyone getting sick in the chat everyone's getting seasick put on one if this shit is trash and put it through you like
Okay, well guys and put it put a put a 10 what a one for me put a one for me in chat because I can't get to Josh
If I get a very $45 in donations within the next couple weeks. I will buy a stream yard
Yeah, I wish I had money to help you
For 20 for my big economy ain't got a lot of money in I'm a regular person
Who said something like that?
And there's more than I had before because it's like,
you know, I can like make money less on like,
I can use apps and I can like, you know,
What I said a one for trash or two for trash one for trash move it for the one there's trash
Should be filled with ones nobody voted
For the one
Anyway, I'm about to delete the app on my phone because this is a waste of storage.
It seems to be recording us too.
I seem to be streaming this as well and money as well because I got this thing running at
I don't see any of that mind that says 20 20 minutes and
About to be 21 minutes. Oh, no, I'm like minds on the pull down, you know, like the the phones like the phones messaging I
Won't down I have to two things running to two things running
Oh, yeah, I see it capture service running upload service running. Yeah, I don't know
So what's it doing? It's recording us to like we're also
Streaming you in your sleep
That's your game of you stream your the way to go
I'm not a lot so I mean it's all
All right later money let's say later thing
I don't even know how to get out of here.
Just leave on the top left.
You can't leave.
You're still in your bed.
Later again.
So there you go.
Oh, there he is.
Oh, look, I'm almost getting you all fat.
How cute.
OK, so let me see.
No, you're not really fat.
So I'm just looking.
I'm actually filling out this thing
where it's like you can do surveys for Google every day.
And then you can, like, they say they give you gifts and stuff.
Yeah
The following social media do I can submit it's a long fucking
Entry survey, but it's Google so
You know you're gonna do it right now. Yeah, I'll talk to you. Hmm. That'll be fun
Well, especially for you. No, yeah in the chat
Oh, that's fine, that's fine, that's fine.
Okay, no, I'm paying full attention to you guys.
So how was your New Year?
Tell me all about it.
Oh, no, you said it was terrible.
He doesn't tell me about it, I heard it was bad.
No, I mean, New Year's Eve, it was quiet.
I just, I was just at home, I didn't do anything.
Well, how was your Christmas?
Christmas was okay, so it was quiet as well.
I'm not a...
I mean, I like the Christmas season, but when it comes to the actual days, like the celebration, I get a little, nah, I don't really...
Get a gift?
No, I don't do gifts.
You don't get one gift on Christmas?
No, we don't do that anymore. I mean, we're all...
We're in our fifties and shit, man. We don't buy gifts for each other anymore.
Well, you don't have like relatives or like, you know...
What do you want me to say? We just we don't do that
I mean when my nephews were younger, yeah, of course
Yeah used to get them gifts all the time, but they're in their 20s now if what do we get him give him cash
No, they don't they call me pheo. Actually, you know, that means God
You know pheo is got pheo is uncle. Oh
Oh, thank you. I got you. Yeah
But it's not it's not it's asking my primary phone number, but it's not working
No matching results found. Come on. Please. Hello. I
Just hate when like I get stuck in the middle of like
And I have to fill it and I'm all let me go and serve it and I cannot fill it because it's not taking them
I'm just gonna close this up. Ah, okay
Hi, hey, you don't like Riverside. I don't know or is I know no. Okay. I got scared. I got scammed. Well, it's free though
It's free. I'm odd criminals
Hey, easy. How are you? Hi loser?
I'm just opening YouTube on my freaking tablet because this is driving me crazy. I can't see chat. I can't see what's going on
Yeah, look at the chat
Maybe I need to do like put them in like little like brackets
What's happening? I'm trying to figure out how to like bypass the security thing
Okay, okay, I'm back OMG by Gotti
Gotti he gave money a wrench and he did he call him trash. I didn't call anybody trash. I
Don't know. I don't know. Maybe I will but it's bad. Okay. Well, what's this?
It's just kidding. Okay. Well, I mean, I don't like how I can't
Make do a presentation. I can share the screen and show the entire screen the window the chrome job. Okay. Yeah, I like I
Mean I can I'm looking at the
At the stream. I don't need to see us to I don't see anything happening
Well, would you like to see the new?
I knew a premiere about the plans for this for the channel and stuff. So here we can take it out. You can watch it with me
Sure, okay, okay perfect perfect perfect
Okay, this is brand new
Okay, got it. Okay here
share the screen
See it that I can see yeah
Welcome in everyone
Starting today, we are beginning a series that has been calling to me for a very long time
the 64 arts and I don't mean arts in the sense of polite little hobbies
I mean arts as powers as skills as codes
Technologies of culture
These are the kinds of human abilities that build kingdoms.
Seduceart create breathtaking butte when arguments, decode symbols, and basically
shape reality.
In the classical Indian tradition, the 60 for arts.
Often called the Chattashasti Kala are a complete map of a cultivated life.
This isn't just about spiritual practice.
It's not just religion, and it's not just creativity.
It's the whole spectrum, music, dance, poetry, painting,
perfumery, cooking, architecture, language, strategy, games, etiquette.
Even how to read signs and moods and social currents.
It's as if someone sat down and asked.
What does it mean to become a fully skilled human being?
And then they wrote a list.
Now, here's what makes this series so exciting for me and I hope for you.
I'm not going to treat the 60 for Arts like a museum exhibit.
Gathering dust behind glass. No, I'm treating them like a spellbook for modern life.
Because every single one of these arts has a then and a now.
Back then, they were part of a refined, educated, and often sacred approach to living.
Especially connected to aesthetics, devotion, romance, and social intelligence. But today.
They are still just as relevant, but we have to translate them
So when we talk about something like music or dance sure, it's still music. It's still dance
The form is recognizable
But when we start talking about things like deciphering messages, creating perfumes, designing
ornaments, the art of conversation, strategy, handwriting, or staging performances, suddenly
we're talking about modern skills like branding, charisma, networking, seduction, influence.
And I absolutely love that.
Now, a quick note.
Because I know for some of you, this might be the first time you're hearing about the 60 for arts.
There are actually different versions of the list depending on the source text you consult.
You'll see variations across different traditions.
That's perfectly normal.
This is unlike the periodic table of elements where everyone agrees on the exact same items in the exact same order.
So, for this series, here's what I'm doing. I'm using a classic, widely recognized framework of the 60 for Arts.
And I'll be sure to point out any interesting variations when it matters.
The goal ISN, T to get bogged down in arguing about the exact wording of a list from a thousand years ago.
The point is to use this list like a living map, one skill at a time.
And ask three key questions. What does this art teach us?
How does practicing it change you?
And, most importantly, how can you practice it today in your own life?
Because here's the deeper secret, the real magic behind this whole concept, the 60 for arts, R&T, just things you do.
They are ways you become. This is about training your attention. It's about refining your desire.
It's about strengthening your expression and expanding your perception.
It's about learning how to consciously shape your experience of the world.
And when you start to take them seriously, something truly wild begins to happen.
Your life gets more designed.
It becomes more intentional, more expressive, more enchanted.
You stop just drifting through your days and you start crafting them.
So, in the coming days and weeks, I'm going to cover these arts mostly one by one.
Some episodes will be quick and punchy-like. Here's the art. Here's what it means.
And here's how you can start practicing it, right now.
Other episodes will be deeper divies.
Especially when an art touches on fascinating subjects like mythology,
Tantra, aesthetics, music theory, or social power dynamics.
And here's the vibe of this series. This is for the builders, the artists, the creators, the performers, the mystics.
It's for people who know that a spiritual life isn't just meditation and prayers.
A spiritual life is also how you speak, or you cook, how you adorn yourself, how you listen, how you flirt.
You're right how you move how you create beauty and how you master your mind through discipline and
If you're sitting there thinking, okay, this sounds interesting, but why should I really care?
Here's why every era its own version of the 64 arts ours just looks different on the surface
For us today these ancient arts become modern skills
They become how you craft your voice, how you build your personal presence,
how you design your environment to support your goals, how you persuade others,
how you perform whether on a stage or in a meeting, how you tell compelling stories,
how you create meaningful rituals in a modern, often secular life.
How you become unforgettable without ever becoming fake.
That's what we're going to be exploring here.
Now, let me just give you a taste of what's included on this list.
Just to spark your curiosity.
We'll be touching on music and rhythm because sound is spellwork.
We'll touch on dance and movement because the body is a language.
We will explore poetry, storytelling, and drama because narratives run people's lives, including your own.
We'll get into drawing, painting, and design because images have the power to reshape attention.
We'll explore perfumes, flowers, ornamentation, clothing, and beauty because aesthetics are not shallow.
They are energetic technology.
They change how you feel and how others perceive you.
We'll dive into games, puzzles, strategy, and mental agility
because mastery isn't just spiritual, it's also cognitive.
We'll cover conversation, wit, and social intelligence.
Because your entire life can change, based on who trusts you, who understands you, and
who wants to collaborate with you.
And yes, we will also touch on the arts that deal with secrecy, coded messaging, and subtle
power.
Because the old texts were honest about this, perception matters, influence matters, and
timing matters.
Each day, or every few days, I'll introduce one art.
I'll explain what it meant in its classical context.
Then, I'll translate it into a modern practice.
And I'll give you a challenge something you can actually do in your life that day.
So this series isn't just information, it's transformation.
Because this isn't about collecting fun facts.
This is training.
Now, one more thing, and this is really important.
The sois-saint-cathats, at their best, are not about ego.
They are about refinement.
Let's talk cat.
The motivation isn't look at me, I'm so skilled.
It's let me become capable.
Let me be skillful in how I speak, how I love, how I create, how I carry myself,
and how I bring more beauty into the world.
It's a path of making your very life into an offering, and that is why it belongs here
on this channel.
So if you're into this idea, do me a favor.
Subscribe to the channel and please turn on the notifications so you don't miss the start
of the journey.
And comment below right now, which art are you most curious about?
Is it music?
poetry, perfume making, strategy, the art of conversation, painting, dance, tell me what
you want to see first and I'll do my best to prioritize the order.
Because we are going to do this together, one art at a time.
And I promise you, by the end of this series, you're going to be sharper, more expressive,
More powerful. All right, let's begin
So how how many episodes in this series 64 I think holy shit
That's just a couple months of episodes
And then I'll do the live kind of based on that of a premiere it is like the animation or the
Yeah, different animated ones and then
Depending on it, and I'll do maybe a mix of media in it too and like I'll do some
Performing on my own so yeah
Good luck. Thank you. I think it's just fun. It's like I just I'm doing it to kind of a pilot program
I would say and I'm gonna be able to like you know have it and document it and
Maybe like you know turn into something bigger. So that'd be really cool. So
Yeah, I'm just thinking of other ways to enjoy my thing. I'm really able to like
Present like things how I want to present them, you know, it's like now I'm able to like
Why now what is it now?
Technology is making it easy. Oh, okay. It's making it easier like for certain things that I can't think the coding
I can't do coding. I can't do like
Like really like just think I can do graphic design where it's like I can like I know how to generate amazing images
But I'm certainly cannot like, you know create anything close to what I can generate
You know, it's like so it's like I know it's like kind of cheating in some ways, but it's not even cheating
I would say it's just like, you know using using the technology just like people use an instrument
He's like people use a computer. It's like, yeah
We're using a computer cheating in life or something like that because people that have one have an advantage over the people that don't
all you burn some mirrored and cells well it's okay you don't have to watch this series if you
don't want to you know it's like it's no one's forced to it's just something that I think it
would be like just helpful information it's just like something that we can be kind of fun that
we can do together and like we can all you know find our relation to the art and it's like I think
also like what's your favorite art favorite art well there's some interesting ones in the 64 divine
arts because some of them are kind of old-fashioned like there's like you know ventriloquism give me a
I would say Mantra is one of my favorite arts.
Mantra is an art?
Is it one of the arts?
Yeah.
Enchanting?
Like, just using your voice in general, I think that would be under, like, singing.
A lot of it would be under, like, singing or using your voice.
Why not the art of seduction?
That's in there too. I mean that's in there. I know so why wouldn't that be your favorite because I don't I don't I'm not a seducer
I'm like not trying to seduce me. I think I'm sexy enough of my own
I have that I showed you that if you saw the Lilith and Scorpio video you can see like I am like just like people sexualize me
Without people sexualize you. Yeah, or they or they make me more sexual than I am like because it's like they think I'm like some kind of
Like horn ball good. It's okay. I just act I play you know, it's like so I'm not really I'm like very very like
Okay, it may be an act you play, but it's what people see right and people just go by what they see
This should be like smart enough to know the difference between like no
Yeah, I know I assume that too when I'm playing when I'm doing an act too, but yeah
Well, some people get people actually believe it. Yeah
But I'm gonna do some good. I'll do a good my leap replacements and whatever
I'm sure like and as they and as I'll do these videos
I'm gonna be basically do all my astrology on them, right and then if you want me to do like your particular
astrology I can make I can make you know, it's like just contact me and stuff like that and I can make you videos
or like a video with like all your astrology in it like I mean like or it's just one particular
sign or placement really something really important I can look up like there's like a lot of things
I can do like I'm really excited like um
Like uh, you need to you need to get a bigger audience that that follows that stuff, right?
I just had a hundred people and so I'm joining. I mean actually I'm getting really good views
I got over a hundred views on several of my other videos just and like like a lot of likes just in a day
And so that's like really good because it's like usually it's like, you know, some of the videos I have like I have like 510 likes but now I'm getting like
Over hundreds of likes and some of the videos
I just gained like 100 subscribers this month and stuff and plus I was gone 19 or 21 days
To the art of rolling of weed. Yeah. Well, I think that's one of them too basket making
The thing is is that most of the people that know you that know who you know of you
Are in this community like, you know, this local
Handle verse whatever it's called and a lot of these people are not into astrology and all that kind of stuff
Well, the guys like they shouldn't be here then because it's like that's what I'm gonna be focusing on
Person I supposed to be doing and maybe I don't know I don't have fun
Just like talking shit and they having people arguing all day. It's like that can be go to be this channel for that
It's like if people do anyway, she has like 80 people in her job, and I have one person
So it's not like, you know, it's not it's like people
Are are not people are already leaving so it's like they're not even here anyway
So it's like if people that are here then
You know on another level, but it's like yeah, if you don't like terror or whatever. This is my business. It's my it's my profession
It's like what I'm really good at and it's visible. It's just one of the things I'm really good at
So if you're not interested in it's fine, but I would say they have passed on so maybe there is some gonna be an art
You're interested in maybe you're interested in something else like the technology
I used to like make the videos and you're interested in like the my cinematography or
My choices are, I don't know, there's like a lot of stuff.
Just comment, like, you know, like, you know,
participate, whatever.
I'm like, you know, I'm just here to like, experiment.
Like, I really do experiment.
Like, I'm just trying to, I'm just trying to.
Yeah, give it a try.
Everyone wants to be the same.
Like, or, oh, yes, just conform to this group.
No, I'm not conforming to this group.
I'm like, maybe like, in this group,
but I'm not, I am not the group, you know?
It's like, I am like.
I'm not like surrounded by the group in a bad way, but I'm like, but it's like I am not the group
I am my own individual, you know
It happens to be associated with certain people
But it's like then there's people I mean everyone's associated within six degrees, right?
I think that is you got a facelift and a facelift. Why do I look better time? Thank you so much
Facelift, you know you look like you look like mr. Magoo
Who you kind of do buddy, but he's kind of cute Jim back as you know. Oh, hello. I missed my girl
Hi time. Happy new year. Everyone else who who am I missing here?
Samantha. Hello. Happy new year
Yeah, but I'll say like what I'm really enjoying is mantra that I mean, it's like a viewer practicing kind of mantra is like
powerful
because for me meditation is like
basically the opposite of what we normally do which is like basically quieting your mind because at any time your mind has like a
Million thoughts going through it, right?
And it's like, you know million and it's like we try to shut down our mind
There's still it's those talking about something and something and something it's very hard to quiet the mind, right?
And so I think that that's the merely the point of minute of meditation
It's gonna be quiet the mind and then you find something to focus on that it's kind of like
Put you into your unconscious where you can just kind of like run that and then it kind of like so if you run a mantra
And just repeat the mantra that kind of takes everything outside of your mind, right?
It's like and you're just concentrating on the mantra as much as you can as close as you can
And then it's like just do a single point and you say it's not easy
And it's like it takes time, but it's like you just continue doing it
You can continue getting a stronger focus on like the just the mantra
What do you go on?
Yeah, and then it's like once you get then you take actually get benefits from it
It's like actually like they have these special effects that you can get from this like and basically just run on your unconscious
And that basically will clear your mind of like a lot of the extraneous thoughts
So we are able to start putting focus on other parts of our life and see
Things that we weren't seeing before and things like that right so
Yeah, that's what I mean. I do a lot of but it's like also
The mantra is the deity in a certain way
So if you are into deities or things like that all the deities are basically the same deity
It's all like just God and a bunch of different masks. They're all just different outfits
You can put on like different costumes or whatever. That's all the deities, right? Because it's like the essence. They're just like the same thing
Whatever we are, right?
and so
Basically, it's like in Tantra and things like that you
You become the deity you don't worship them you either have like a partnership with them or you actually
Invoke them into yourself and you become that deity and you and you like become in the vessel for that deity to like live on earth
in a certain way to just kind of share
and
Share some of its power with you too like or their power right
But it's like not all about trying to gather power from different deities or whatever
It's like if some of these relationships we've had prior to this this incarnation, right?
It's like we I mean it's like so we were we have a
There's so much more going behind the scenes that we're trying to be Highlander. Aren't you you're you're
Be Highlander who's Highlander is that here? This is not a leather jacket. This is like a vibe
This is like a cheap like a little like a puppy jacket. It's not it's not a leather jacket about blogger, you know
So anyway, oh, you're just making fun of me. Okay, well my money. Yeah, I was just playing with you. It's okay
Well, yeah, so I think this is the only brave one
Okay, you're gonna sleep. Okay. Well, that's what happens when you smoke so much weed money for 20 and but you can't can't hang with us
So I've been like lighting this incense. I have this amazing incense. It's like I'm doing some right now
This this one is
Copal you heard of copal
What it's just called copal or copal. Oh, no, I haven't heard of it. It says
Hold on, we're getting the glasses. It says, natural resin, dipterocarpacea
shore from Indonesia, used to cleanse, purify, and protect,
creates sacred spaces and clears negative energy, inspires creativity, abundance, and love.
So how does that sound? That sounds good, and I have this little chart over here.
So do you burn it?
Yeah, it's like a self-lighting charcoal.
So I put it on the charcoal and it'll start.
Oh, okay.
You see it?
Yep, yep.
It's like a, it's really hot.
Oh my God, it's very hot, okay.
It smells so good, it smells so good.
It's like the-
Look at all the smoke coming off the thing.
Ah, this is a real deal of incense.
This is a real, ah.
Look at this, it's going.
Yeah, it's normal. Yeah, it's just burns. It's just it's smokes. It smells so good though. It's really good insight
I mean, that's what happens. I put too much on I think but yeah, look at it go and it's going it's rising so fast, too
Smells so good though. You see spirit. You can see spirits in the smoke and stuff
Do I see nothing also something scary, so this is like my Lilith
I got a little bit. This is scary because I did it because Lilith is supposed to be kind of scared
You know Lilith is
Yeah, yeah, vaguely. Yeah. Okay. Well, I
Did not my astrology placement with Lilith. She's gonna make my 10th house
Which is the house of Capricorn usually and it's like a reputation, but it's like
Or probably your public your public stance or whatever, but
Yeah, I'll let you watch it
Here we go. So see if you like this one. I think this is you'll let me watch it. You'll let me watch it like I'm gonna bless you with this here watch this
Here we go
Today, we're diving into one of the most intense
Misunderstood and powerful placements in the entire Zodiac. Lilac and Scorpio in the 10th house
Let's be clear. This is not a cute little placement
This is the energy that walks into a room and changes the temperature, even if the person says nothing at all.
So let's break down the pieces first to understand what we're dealing with.
Lilith or Black Moon Lilith in astrology is the symbol of the part of us that refuses to be domesticated.
It's that raw edge, the hunger we were shamed for, the truth we were told to soften.
It shows where we then projected onto, scapegoated, sexualized, demonized.
or where we've had to reclaim a part of ourselves a society didn't want us to own.
Next, Scorpio.
Scorpio is the sign of intensity, secrecy, desire, transformation, death and rebirth,
psychological x-ray vision, and power dynamics Scorpio doesn't do small talk.
Scorpio does what's the real motive? What are you avoiding?
What's the shadow behind that smile?
And finally, the 10th house.
This is your public life, your career, reputation, status, authority, legacy,
What you're known for, the role you play in the world and how the world judges you.
So, when you put all three together, what do you get?
A person whose public life is deeply intertwined with taboo themes, power, truth, intimacy,
control, betrayal, exposure, and transformation.
This is the placement of someone who can become incredibly influential in the public eye,
while also being profoundly misunderstood.
Because Lilith in the 10th house often marks someone who triggers authority structures just by existing, you might not even be trying to.
You simply exist in a way that exposes what's fake.
Now, let's talk about how this actually shows up in life.
The major theme is what I call the reputation projection.
Lilith in the 10th house is famous for being a projection magnet people assume things about you they assign motives to you
They might sexualize your ambition demonize your confidence or take your very presence as a threat
With Scorpia's influence this projection intensifies
People don't just assume you're ambitious. They assume you're ruthlessly strategic. They don't just assume you're private
They assume you're hiding something dark
And here's the brutal part, sometimes you get punished for what people imagine you
are, not for what you actually did.
This can look like vicious workplace politics, mere campaigns, weird jealousy from bosses
or authority figures, or people constantly trying to humble you for having too much
power, charisma, intelligence, or influence.
The second theme is the Shadow CEO.
Lilith and Scorpio in the 10th often creates someone who can operate behind the scenes
Even if you're a kind and ethical person, you are wired to understand systems.
You know how influence works.
You can read rooms, you can sense hidden agendas.
You know who is lying, who is posturing, and who is terrified underneath their confident
exterior.
This gives you a natural talent for fields like crisis management, investigation, psychology,
occult studies, trauma healing, forensics, finance, strategy, or peer anything that involves
You're the person who can walk into chaos and calmly say,
Okay, here's what's really happening.
But there's a price. You really get to be naive. You're simply not built for it.
This leads us to the third theme, authority wounds.
The 10th house is connected to all forms of authority bosses, institutions,
even the father archetype in some systems, and the general idea of the world's rules.
With Lilith here, there's often a deep wound around authority.
Maybe you were controlled, judged, shamed, or punished publicly.
Maybe you were told to be smaller, quieter, less intense, less sexual, less powerful.
In Scorpio, this story becomes about power and control.
You may have lived through moments where someone tried to dominate you professionally.
You've seen the dark side of authority up close, the manipulation, the coercion, the hindills, the exploitation.
And because Scorpio learns through extremes, you might have had to burn down an old identity
completely just to build your real one.
That's why this placement is so often linked to reinvention.
People with this placement don't just change jobs.
They shapeshift.
Our fourth theme is the Taboo Calling.
Lilith plus Scorpio can't help it, it's drawn to Taboo truths like a magnet.
Your public calling often involves making these taboo topics public in a way that forces
people to deal with reality.
This could be exposing corruption, talking about sexuality without shame, confronting
abuse dynamics, challenging societal double standards, or pulling back the curtain on
a system that pretends it's clean and perfect.
This is why this placement can create such polarizing public figures.
Other people will hate you like you're a fundamental threat to their world.
You have to learn not to negotiate your truth for acceptance.
Now let's go into the shadow of the shadow.
Theme 5 is Power Image and the Trap.
Willowth in the tank can become obsessed with reputation because for you, reputation becomes a survival mechanism.
If you've been misunderstood or scapegoated your whole life, you might over-correct by trying to control the narrative obsessively.
And Scorpio loves control.
So the trap is becoming so strategic about your public image that you stop being emotionally
free.
Another trap is using power as armor.
Scorpio can weaponize distance.
Lilith can weaponize defiance.
So if you've been hurt, you might adopt a percent of that says, no one can touch me.
But your healing journey is about learning the difference between healthy privacy and
self-imposed isolation.
Because you don't actually want to be untouchable.
You want to be respected for who you truly are.
Next, Theme 6.
Sexuality and Status.
This is where things can get weird, so I'll say it cleanly.
Lilith can symbolize sexuality, but more specifically, the part of sexuality that society tries to control, shame, or exploit.
In the 10th house, this can show up as your sexuality being entangled with your public identity, whether through how people perceive you,
how you're treated, or what you're allowed to be in the public eye.
Scorpia adds a layer of magnetism and intensity, a kind of presence that people read as erotic
even when you're literally just sitting there drinking coffee.
This is why boundaries are non-negotiable with this placement.
Not because you're too much, but because other people will constantly try to define
you as a symbol instead of a person.
Finally, we arrive at the highest expression of this placement.
When Lilith and Scorpio in the 10th house is fully integrated, it becomes a public force of transformation.
Not a motivational poster, a transformer.
Someone who tells the truth that actually heals, because it stops the lies.
Someone who can lead without playing nice with corruption.
Someone who can hold immense power without abusing it.
That's incredibly rare.
And that's why this placement is both so difficult and so destined for greatness.
So, let me give you some practical tells and medicine, because this placement needs a strategy.
If you have this placement, you should assume three things.
One, your career path won't be linear.
You're built for evolution, so expect major reinventions.
Two, people will project onto you.
Don't take every accusation personally.
Not everything is about you, some of it is about their own fear of intensity.
Lilith gives you an edge.
The only way this combination stays beautiful is if you commit to integrity, especially
when it would be easier to just retaliate.
And here are three medicine practices for this placement.
First, practice narrative control without paranoia.
Document your work.
Keep receipts.
Not because you're petty, but because you are dealing with constant projection.
Second, choose your battles wisely.
Scorpio is surgical. Strike only where it truly matters.
And third, build a public mission that can't be reduced to gossip.
When you are mission-led, smirk campaigns don't stick as easily.
Because the core truth of Lilith and Scorpio in the 10th house is this.
You are not here to be liked.
You're here to be real. You're not here to follow a script.
You're here to rewrite one.
and the world will test you over and over by trying to shame you back into silence.
But your power is that you can turn shame into authority.
You can take the very parts of yourself you are told to hide and make them the foundation of your legacy.
And when you stop fearing the spotlight,
you become the very thing Scorpio always promises, a phoenix with a job title.
Not just surviving, leading, thank you so much for watching.
If this resonated, don't forget to like, subscribe and share with someone who needs to hear it.
See you next time
Interesting interesting. Yeah, that's my pretty long. Yeah. Well, they're like between five and ten minutes
I think is like with the basic attention span of
people someone about nine minutes, but I think it
I mean, if you're a Scorpio, if you're a little thin Scorpio, if you're a Scorpio, if you're
a 10th house person, it means that all the, I mean, all those things can have relevance
to you.
I mean, it's not just for the people that is like specific, but if people do have requests
and things, let me know and stuff, and maybe I'll, you know, get somebody else's some,
some placements.
I just came back in time, are you asking me if I'm on vacation?
No, I'm not he's in the hospital with it. He's
No, I'm in a motel, but
Yeah, I've been dealing with hospital. You have a prostitute in there with you. No, you know
Oh, why'd you look like you said it? I kind of like laughed a little bit
Because I don't I don't do that. Did you get so nervous?
I'm not nervous
No, you're about a prostitute
Nope, never are you sure? Yeah, I'm positive
You're at your wallet stolen by a
Woman of the night nope
If you ever caught your girlfriend
Turning tricks for no no you ever dated flurry diamond. Nope
Okay, you're clean. Okay. Thanks. Bye scarlet
Happy new year
Yeah, sassy scarlet
Hi sassy
Yeah
So we're just having like a little pow wow today. I was showing some stuff. Hey, can you see you don't see this one?
There's no doing hearts for you
Thanks time. Can you go like this? Can you raise your hand like that? Hello?
What do you see anything where there's not like things they're not like the bunch of things you can do that are so fun
Like that. I don't see anything. I don't even see it on the screen like on the stream
This is not working. This is just not working out
Okay, mics, you know what's good though is like the microphones seem to work better than any but they didn't
The microphones are just notoriously never working and so let's say you know the microphones work
It's just that yours is never close to your mouth
You want my mouth closer to you, okay? Nope. Hey, you know, it's really cool that I do I have a 432 player
Like do you know about like the HZ of a
of music it's all at like 440 all every but it's like 430 oh yeah yeah the
frequency yeah but it's everything that 440 but 430 440 is the a note that's the
frequency of the a okay but what's 432
G I guess I don't know I'll look it up on
432 HZ is it says it is
The 432 frequency is a musical tuning used since ancient times by various cultures due
to the harmonizing effect on the body and mind.
It's sound resonates with the mathematical pattern found in nature and is considered
a tool for well-being in the expansion of consciousness, and then it says, it's a musical
tuning that maintains a mathematical relationship with nature.
Um, it says, Pythagorean music was based on mathematically perfect scales.
Well, Egypt and India specific sounds were used to induce deep meditative states.
Many ancient instruments were used to vibrate at 432.
Anyway, I have this little app or like this little thing that makes everything 432.
Oh my God, you're all wet.
What?
When Nordic came back all wet and she shook and she's all wet.
I don't know, but I think it does work though, I mean it's like, isn't it weird, like it's like a little bit off from like what would be the best thing to be listening to, like the best music for our brain is like a little bit off to throw us like a little bit off.
I don't know.
Chaotic looking and then there's like others other ones that are that are more in order like the 440s
That there is the chaotic and the 432s like it orderly is like in nice shapes and stuff
So I don't know I looked at the
Frequency if you get a good a good tuner like a good guitar tuner. They'll you can change the frequency too
I'll show you a picture of what it looks like
Oh, excuse me so sorry. Okay. Okay. Oh, maybe I can I have to share the screen. Hold on. Okay.
Share screen.
And right here. Do you see this one? Do you see it? Yeah. Yeah. So that's the 432.
And it's all like night design, sort of like rays, like a sun. And this one looks like it's like a
It's not exploded or something, you know, but what is it? What's making the light?
Well, this is like they're like they're just like sheets of metal
And then they they put the frequency on the metal and they have sand on it and then the sand
Oh, I see that's where it vibrates the
It vibrates the like the platform. Yeah, I know what you're talking about
There are like examples of it. I think it's like yes
It's like this one. I mean it's like the same thing basically. It's just like it looks like this is all like kind of chaotic and like crowded and like, you know
And this is like all
Symmetrical and beautiful and stuff. I don't know. It's okay. I have to know. You don't know
I don't know about this stuff
Yeah, well, I mean it's like they they've said like oh here's a sound thing
They've said that's 345 hc on this like these plates. Yeah makes like circles and stuff. I mean, that's pretty amazing
Make the circle with
You play a frequency so that proves that sound is form, right and here's more of it here through this one
Proves that sound is form. What do you mean?
Right because because it frequencies it creates all these different patterns
Um, okay, I can have you ever seen that like I'll show you guys I think I can find a video. I know. Yeah, I know. Mm-hmm. I
Know what you mean, but
I'll show you home
Okay, so here's do you see the screen
Right here seeing sound with sound waves is like four minutes long
let's see you see the screen the vibration pattern revealed by the sand occurs at what's
known as a natural frequency of the metal plate this is a specific frequency at which
the plate naturally vibrates and produces sound and this is part of what's making up the sound
when i hit the plate but it's not all of it because if you keep turning the frequency up there's more
So it's the resonance of the metal itself.
And so here we are up at 426 Hz and suddenly out of that mess there's another pattern of vibration, beautiful pattern on the plate here.
Platni's experiment reveals how a simple object, this metal plate, can produce a complex sound.
Because it doesn't just vibrate at one frequency.
it has many natural frequencies each corresponding to a different pattern of
vibration i'm not asking for them
when you hit the plate what happens is that lots of those vibration patterns
all happen at the same time one on top of the other
Each one contributes their natural frequency to the mix
and that combination is what makes up the sound that you hear.
Every object that vibrates has its own combination of natural frequencies
determined by its physical characteristics and together these frequencies form a unique acoustic
So there's a beautiful relationship between an object and the sound that it produces
When you hear a sound you're hearing messages about the thing that created it its size its shape
What it's made from even how the object was made
What do you think yeah, I mean the stuff stuff is interesting and all that I just don't think it's mystical
I don't think there's like some hidden thing going on
That you don't think it's interesting that vibrations create these like of these like perfect patterns
It is interesting, but again, it's the resonance of the metal itself, right? Well, how about the human body is that do we have resonances that we can maybe
Have in our brain and stuff like that. No, I doubt it. I mean, we're not a
We're not a solid a solid
Whatever, you know, we're not I saw that frequency we have a voice
That's a frequency that comes out of our body that we had put different vibrations to it
You know what I do mantra is like you can vibrate certain parts with it and it will have an effect
I mean, it's like it starts you start to feel it. It's like
It's hard to explain, but okay, but yeah, but it will open like it will start this energy coming up your spine and stuff like that
If you use the right ones, right?
I would say seek out a guru, whatever, but I mean, I
Have been initiated
But you know, you can like there are safe things to do like you can do the Ganesha Ganesha
Montre like Om Gum Ganapatayinamaha or let's do that
That's like two-year-olds do that in India, right? It's like that's like it's like they
They grow up on that like and it's like and that's like
very like it's like it's like a Mickey Mouse to us is like Ganesha to India it's
like in the next and like the the gods are a lot like superheroes in some ways
right and it's kind of like we have a superhero kind of thing going on here
too we're being or protecting blah blah we're doing this we're saving the world
blah blah we're like these special we have special powers we're mutants for
special technology words are vibration words are so powerful that's why I
called spells spelling spells and they have a big you know addiction dick I'm
They have, you know, cursive, cursing, right?
And it's like, there's like a lot of different,
like words you can attribute to like how words and,
you know, the language is originally created
as like a commerce for commerce thing,
by the Phoenicians, right?
Cause they would be sailing around
and they would have to have a language they understood
to like know who else was there and blah, blah, blah,
and be able to make, you know,
it does to a great advantage
to people that could speak the language.
but not everyone could. And they were basically just kept to mystery schools and for the elite to
have language until a certain time like now it's like now we just take it for granted that everybody
has access to everything and they have like you know laptops in the middle of Africa and stuff
but it's like yeah at one time like you know people control the language and there are
New ways of controlling language too, because that's like all the new all the new words that come out and things and
The secret when you speak ugly you stand lower vibration, which attracts negative energy
I know someone goes like it off Hitler to like a glass of water and they look at the molecules
And there's like an angry man with a mustache
It must be true they showed me this is more emotional
There was that Japanese guy remember that the Japanese guy who tried to yeah
Who tried doing that like
in viewing it for you viewing
Materials with with thoughts whatever like water and then freezing it or whatever
Experiments, yeah, exactly. Yeah. Yeah, those you went on to found Bitcoin
No, we didn't
I know I get so confused all Japanese people look at what I'm just kidding
I think it was just a joke.
I mean, I'm in trouble.
You are upset.
I've upset you.
You look for Lorne in fact.
For Lorne.
Yeah, looks so sad.
Oh, I want to go get a coffee.
OK, go grab one.
No, I mean, I don't have to hear.
I have to go drive and get one.
Well, it was fabulous talking to you as always, you know, you know, I love you, you know, I love bald guys
You're just like, you know, a delight
Always a fun time
Thank you thing that is for being here. Hey, yeah, I'll go. Okay. Okay. Bye
Go get out of here
Jesus, where's ghost how come he's not here? He fell asleep drunk. Oh
That's so unusual
Yeah
Okay, well, okay, I'm just kidding. I love you think that is yeah, you know rub your bald head have a good night
Yeah, right. It was nice talking to you again. I'll I'll talk to you probably in a couple days. I guess
Okay, okay. I'm all right your dad and you know, God bless you on my heart. Yeah. Thank you again, but
Like I said before it's a relief. It's better this way
For him to like for everyone
So
Anyway, so yeah tomorrow we got to deal with
cremation and all that stuff
Well, I
Hope you have a wonderful day. Yeah, I'm sure it'll be great
All right guys everyone. What I said bye take care. I'm still gonna be watching. I mean if you keep going
I'm still gonna be watching while I drive to get a copy. All right. Okay. Bye
Bye-bye get out of here. Okay. Let's get him
He's gone guys. Oh my gosh, I thought he'd never go
Thing that is
He's more than gold think that is
This is excuse me first I can just work it on my website a little bit. Okay, let me go see if this works
Everything's just so expensive ask you anything. Okay. How about that?
Okay, guys. Well, everyone's just mad at me. Okay. Good night, guys. I'll be back. I'll be back some other time
Give me a good night guys. Love you